Jascha Heifetz Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1911-1974 (Box 1-247)
  - Music by Other Composers (Box-folder 15/2-11, Box 16-247)
    - Composers
      - Prokofiev, Sergei
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 80, F minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 140/7)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, op. 94, D major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 141/1)
        - [Sonata, violins (2), op. 56, C major], Violin parts (Box-folder 141/2)
        - Le pas d'acier, Orchestral score (Box-folder 141/3)
        - [Summer day suite, op. 65a], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Symphony, no. 5, op. 100], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Symphony, no. 7, op. 131, C-sharp minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 141/4)
      - Provost, Heinz
        - Intermezzo, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 141/5)
      - Puccini, Giacomo
        - La Bohème, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 142/1)
      - Rabinof, Sylvia
        - [Deluge cantata, mixed chorus, oboe, timpani, piano], Ozalid of ms. score (Box-folder 245/1)
        - Profile-J.H., Holograph piano score (Box-folder 142/2)
        - Profile-J.H., Ozalid of holograph revised piano score (Box-folder 142/2)
        - Rika (Profile no. II), Piano score (Box-folder 142/3)
      - Rachmaninoff, Sergei
        - [Concerto, piano, no. 3, op. 30, D minor], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 142/4)
        - [Etudes-tableaux, op. 39], Piano score (Box-folder 142/5)
        - Romance, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 142/6)
        - Humoresque, Piano score (Box-folder 142/7)
        - [Preludes, op. 23], Piano score (Box-folder 142/8)
        - [Sonata, cello, piano, op. 19, G minor], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 142/9)
        - Wenn Nacht mich hüllt und Schweigen, Piano-vocal score; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 143/1)
        - O, schönes Mädchen, lasse nie, Piano-vocal score (2) (Box-folder 143/2)
        - Frühlingsfluten, Piano-vocal score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 143/3)
        - Lilacs, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 143/4)
        - [Suite, pianos (2), op. 17], Piano parts (Box-folder 143/5)
        - Trio élégiaque, Piano score and parts (Box-folder 143/6)
        - [Vocalise, op. 34, no. 14; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 143/7)
        - [Works, vocal. Selections], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 143/8)
      - Rameau, Jean-Philippe
        - [Tambourin; arr.], Arranger's holograph (Joseph Achron) violin part (Box-folder 143/9)
        - [Tambourin; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 143/9)
      - Ravel, Maurice
        - [Bolero; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 143/10)
        - [Bolero; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 144/1)
        - Pastourelle, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 144/2)
        - [Ma mère l'oye. Selections; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 144/3)
        - [Pièce en forme de habenera; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 144/4)
        - [Quartet, strings], Parts (Box-folder 144/5)
        - [Sonata, violin, cello], Parts (Box-folder 144/6)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 144/7)
        - [Sonatine, piano. Menuett; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 144/8)
        - [Sonatine, piano. Menuett; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 144/9)
        - [Le Tombeau de Couperin, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Le Tombeau de Couperin, orchestra. Rigaudon; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 144/10)
        - [Trio, piano, strings], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 144/11)
        - [Tzigane, violin, orchestra], Orchestral score (Box-folder 144/12)
        - [Tzigane, violin, orchestra], Parts (Box-folder 144/13)
        - [Tzigane, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 145/1)
        - [La valse, orchestra], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [La valse; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 145/2)
        - [La valse; arr.], 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 145/3)
      - Rawsthorne, Alan
        - [Quartet, clarinet, strings], Score (Box-folder 145/4)
        - [Quartet, strings], Score (Box-folder 145/5)
      - Reger, Max
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 109, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 145/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 121, F-sharp major], Parts (Box-folder 145/7)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 141a, G major], Parts (Box-folder 145/8)
        - [Sextet, strings, op. 118, F major], Parts (Box-folder 146/1)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op 84, F-sharp major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 146/2)
        - [Walzer-Capricen, op. 9], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 146/3)
      - Respighi, Ottorino
        - Quartetto dorico, Parts (Box-folder 146/4)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, B minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 146/5)
      - Riego, Teresa
        - O dry those tears, Organ-vocal score with violin obbligato part (Box-folder 146/6)
      - Ries, Franz
        - Perpetuum mobile, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 146/7)
        - Capriccio, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 146/8)
      - Rieti, Vittorio
        - [Quartet, strings, F major], Parts (Box-folder 146/9)
      - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nicolai
        - [Capriccio espagnol, op. 35], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - Chants nationaux russes, Piano-vocal score; collected and edited by Rimsky-Korsakov (Box-folder 146/10)
        - [Fantasy on Russian themes; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 146/11)
        - Hymn to the sun, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 146/12)
        - [Kaschey bessmertny; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 147/1)
        - [Mlada; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 147/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, no.1 op. 12, F major], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Quartet, strings, no.1 op. 12, F major], Parts (Box-folder 147/3)
        - [Scheherazade, orchestra, op. 35], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Scheherezade, orchestra, op. 35; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 147/4)
        - [Skazka o tsare Saltane; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 147/5)
        - [Snegurochka; arr.], Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 148/1)
        - Aimant le rose, le rossignol, Piano-vocal score (2) (Box-folder 148/2)
        - La fiancée du tzar, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 148/3)
      - Robledo, Julian
        - Three o'clock in the morning, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 148/4)
      - Rode, Pierre
        - Caprices, Violin score (Box-folder 148/5)
      - Rodgers, Richard
        - Falling in love with love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 148/6)
        - Many a new day, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 149/1)
        - People will say we're in love, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 149/2)
        - With a song in my heart, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 149/3)
      - Roger-Ducasse, Jean
        - Allegro appasionato, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 149/4)
      - Romberg, Sigmund
        - [Deep in my heart, dear; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 149/5)
      - Röntgen, Julius
        - [Trio, strings, op. 76], Parts (Box-folder 149/6)
      - Roussel, Paul
        - [Quartet, strings, B minor], Parts (Box-folder 149/7)
      - Rózsa, Miklós
        - [Concert overture, op. 26], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24], Ozalid of ms. orchestral score (Box-folder 245/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24; arr.], Ozalid of holograph [?] piano-violin score and part; Heifetz's suggested revisions on the score (Box-folder 149/8)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24; arr.], Ozalid of of holograph [?] piano-violin score and part; revised version (Box-folder 149/9)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part; first version (Box-folder 149/10)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 24; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part; revised edition (Box-folder 149/11)
        - Duo, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 149/12)
        - [Nordungarische Bauerlieder und Tänze, op. 5], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 150/1)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 22], Miniature (Box 213)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 22], Parts (Box-folder 150/2)
        - Concerto per violino. violoncello ed orchestra, Ozalid of ms. piano-violin-cello score (Box-folder 245/3)
        - Concerto per violine. violoncello ed orchestra, Ozalid of holograph [?] violin-cello score; Without second movement (p. 26-41) (Box-folder 150/3)
        - [Sinfonia concertante, op. 29; arr.], Piano score and violin and cello parts (Box-folder 150/4)
        - [Sonata, violins (2), op. 15], Parts (Box-folder 150/5)
        - [Tema con variazioni, op. 29a], Ozalid of holograph [?] score (Box-folder 150/6)
        - [Tema con variazioni, op. 29a; arr.], Ozalid of holograph [?] piano score and violin and cello parts (Box-folder 150/7)
        - [Tema con variazioni, op. 29a; arr.], Printed piano score and violin and cello parts (Box-folder 150/8)
        - [Theme, variations, and finale, op. 13], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [The vintner's daughter, op. 23], Piano score (Box-folder 151/1)
      - Rubinstein, Anton
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 52, B-flat major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 151/2)
      - Rubinstein, Beryl
        - Twelve definitions, Piano score (Box-folder 151/3)
        - Fantasy, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 151/4)
        - Fantasy, Photostat of holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 151/4)
        - [Suite, pianos (2)], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Each movement bound separately (Box-folder 151/5)
      - Saint-Saëns, Camille
        - [Concerto, cello, op. 33, A minor; arr.], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 151/6)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 61, B minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 152/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 61, B minor], Parts (Box-folder 152/2-4)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 61, B minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 152/5)
        - [Fantasie, piano, harp, op. 124], Parts (Box-folder 153/1)
        - [Havanaise, violin, orchestra, op. 83], Orchestral score (Box-folder 153/2)
        - [Havanaise, violin, orchestra, op. 83], Parts (Box-folder 153/3)
        - [Havanaise, op. 83; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 153/4)
        - [Introduction and Rondo Capriccioso, violin, orchestra, op. 28], Orchestral score (Box-folder 153/5)
        - [Introduction and Rondo Capriccioso, violin, orchestra, op. 28], Parts (Box-folder 153/6-7)
        - [Introduction and Rondo Capriccioso, op. 28; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 153/8)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 75, D minor], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 154/1)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 18], Piano-score and part (Box-folder 154/2)
      - Sammetini, Giovanni Battista
        - [Sonatas, violins (2), bass, op. 7; arr.], Piano score and violin parts (Box-folder 154/3)
      - Santorsola, Guido
        - [Chôro, no. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 154/4)
      - Sarasate, Pablo
        - [Caprice Basque, op. 24], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 154/5)
        - [Carmen fantasy, violin, orchestra, op. 25], Parts (Box-folder 155/1-3)
        - [Carmen fantasy, op. 25; arr.], Piano-violin score (2) and parts (3) (Box-folder 155/4)
        - [Introduction et tarantelle, violin, orchestra, op. 43], Orchestral score (Box-folder 155/5)
        - [Introduction et tarantelle, violin, orchestra, op. 43], Parts (Box-folder 155/6)
        - [Introduction et tarantelle, op. 43; arr], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (4) (Box-folder 155/7)
        - [Spanische Tänze, op. 21], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 156/1)
        - [Spanische Tänze, op. 22], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 156/2)
        - [Spanische Tänze, op. 26], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 156/3)
        - [Zigeunerwiesen, violin, orchestra, op. 20], Orchestral score (Box-folder 156/4)
        - [Zigeunerwiesen, violin, orchestra, op. 20], Parts (Box-folder 156/5)
        - [Zigeunerwiesen, op. 20; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (3) (Box-folder 156/6)
      - Sauret, Emile
        - [Berceuse, op. 2, no. 1], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 156/7)
        - [Grandes etudes, op. 24], Violin score; 3 vols. (Box-folder 156/8)
      - Scalero, Rosario
        - [Suite im alten Stil, op. 15], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 156/9)
      - Scarlatti, Domenico
        - Opere complete per clavicembalo, Harpsichord score; Folders: 157/1 Vols. 1-2 157/2 Vols. 3-4 158/1 Vols. 5-6 158/2 Vols. 7-8 159/1 Vols. 9-10 159/2 Supplemental vol. (Box-folder 157/1-2, Box-folder 158/1-2, Box-folder 159/1-2)
      - Schelling, Ernest
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Edited by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 159/3)
      - Schoenberg, Arnold
        - [Verklärte Nacht, string sextet, op. 4], Miniature score (Box 213)
      - Schradieck, Henry
        - The school of violin-technics, Violin score; 2 vols. (books 1 and 3) (Box-folder 160/1)
      - Schubert, François
        - L'abeille, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 160/2)
      - Schubert, Franz Peter
        - [Adagio and rondo concertante, D. 487, F major], Piano score and violin, viola, cello parts (Box-folder 160/3)
        - [Ave Maria, D. 840; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by August Wilhelmj (Box-folder 160/4)
        - Duos, Piano-violin score and part; Different edition of above (Box-folder 160/5-6)
        - [Deutsche Tänze, D. 783, no. 10, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2); Arranged by Sam Franko; Arranged by Joseph Achron (Box-folder 160/7)
        - Fantasia/symphonically arranged for piano and orchestra by Franz Liszt, 2 piano (4 hands) score (2) (Box-folder 161/1)
        - [Impromptus, D. 899], Piano score (Box-folder 161/2)
        - [Impromptus, D. 935], Piano score (Box-folder 161/3)
        - [Marches militaires, no. 1, D. 733, D major; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 161/4)
        - [Moments musicaux, no. 3, D. 780, A-flat major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 161/5)
        - [Octet, strings, D. 803, F major], Parts (Box-folder 161/6)
        - [Quartets, strings], Parts (Box-folder 161/7)
        - [Quartetsatz, D. 703, C minor], Parts; First edition (1870) (Box-folder 162/1)
        - [Quintet, piano, violin, viola, cello, bass, D. 667, A major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 162/2)
        - [Quintet, strings, D. 956, C major], Parts (Box-folder 162/3)
        - [Rosamunde, D. 797. Overture], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Rosamunde, D. 797, no. 9. Ballet; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 162/4)
        - Rondo, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 162/5)
        - [Sonatinas, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 162/6)
        - [Symphony, no. 9, D. 944, C major; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 163/1)
        - [Symphonies. Selections.], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Trios, piano, strings], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 163/2)
        - [Trio, strings, no. 1, D. 471, B-flat major], Parts; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 163/3)
        - [Trio, strings, no. 2, D. 581, B-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 163/4)
        - [Valses sentimentales, no. 13, D. 779, A major; arr.], Arranger's holograph (Achron) piano-violin score; Laid in: Unidentified holograph (Achron) labeled "Violino I" (Box-folder 163/5)
        - [Valses sentimentales, no. 13, D. 779, A major; arr.], Copyist ms. of violin part (Box-folder 163/5)
        - [Valses sentimentales, no. 13, D. 779, A major; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 163/5)
        - Kammermusik, Miniature score (Box 213)
        - Klavierwerke, Piano score (Box-folder 163/6)
        - Tänze, 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 163/7)
      - Schumann, Robert
        - [Andante and variations, op. 46], 2 piano, 4 hands score; 2 copies (Box-folder 164/1)
        - [Concerto, cello, op. 129, A minor; arr.], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 164/2)
        - [Manfred, orchestra, op. 115], Miniature score (Box 213)
        - [Myrthen, op. 25, no. 1. Widmung; arr.], Arranger's holograph (Leopold Auer) piano-violin score (Box-folder 164/3)
        - [Myrthen, op. 25, no. 1. Widmung; arr.], Printed piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 164/3)
        - [Phantasiestücke, op. 73], Piano-clarinet score and clarinet and violin parts (Box-folder 164/4)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, op. 47, E-flat major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 164/5)
        - [Quartets, strings], Parts (Box-folder 164/6)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 44, E-flat major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 164/7)
        - [Romanzen, op. 94, no. 2; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 165/1)
        - [Sonatas, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 165/2)
        - [Symphonies. Selections], Miniature score; band I (Box 213)
        - [Symphonies. Selections], Miniature score; band II (Box 213)
        - [Trios, piano, strings], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 165/3)
        - [Waldscenen, op. 82. Vogel als Prophet; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 165/4)
        - Lieder/Band I, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 165/5)
      - Schwartz, Arthur
        - Dancing in the dark, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 165/6)
      - Scott, Cyril
        - Cherry ripe, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 165/7)
        - Danse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 165/8)
        - Fantasie orientale, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 166/1)
        - Fantasie orientale, Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 166/1)
        - Gentle maiden, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 166/2)
        - Little folk-dance, Piano score and violin and cello parts (Box-folder 166/3)
        - [Lotus land; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 166/4)
        - A song from the east, Piano score (Box-folder 166/5)
        - Tallahassee suite, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 166/6)
      - Scott, Glenn
        - Chopsticks boogie, Piano score (Box-folder 166/7)
      - Scriabin, Alexander
        - [Feuillet d'album; arr.], Arranger's holograph (Arcady Dubensky) piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 166/8)
        - Poème de l'extase, Orchestral score (Box-folder 166/9)
        - [Symphony, op. 26], Orchestral score (Box-folder 166/10)
        - [Symphony, op. 29], Orchestral score (Box-folder 167/1)
      - Sessions, Roger
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 167/2)
      - Ševčík, Otakar
        - Schule der Violintechnik, Violin score (Box-folder 167/3)
      - Sgambati, Giovanni
        - [Serenata napoletana, violin, orchestra, op. 24, no. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 167/5)
        - [Serenata napoletana, violin, orchestra, op. 24, no. 2; arr.], Orchestral parts (Box-folder 167/6)
      - Shebalin, Vissarion
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, op. 29], Score (Box-folder 167/7)
      - Shostakovich, Dmitri
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 99, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 167/8)
        - [Danses fantastiques, op. 1; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 167/9)
        - [Pieces, string octet, op. 11], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Preludes, op. 34; arr], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 168/1)
        - [Symphony, no. 1, op. 10], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 3, op. 20], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 5, op. 47], Miniature score; Various editions (2) (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 7, op. 60], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 9, op. 70], Miniature score (Box 214)
      - Shulman, Alan
        - [Suite on American folk songs], Ozalid of ms. piano-violin score and part; Note: no. 4 only (Box-folder 168/2)
      - Sibelius, Jean
        - Nocturne, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 168/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47, D minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 168/4)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47, D minor], Parts (Box-folder 168/5-8, Box-folder 169/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 47, D minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 169/2)
        - [Humoresque, violin, orchestra, no. 4, op. 89, no. 2; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 169/3)
        - Mélisande, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 169/4)
        - Voces intimae, Parts (Box-folder 169/5)
        - [Symphony, no. 1, op. 39, E minor], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 2, op. 43, D major], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 4, op. 63, A minor], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 5, op. 82, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Symphony, no. 7, op. 105], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Valse triste, op. 44], Orchestral score and parts (Box-folder 169/6)
      - Sieczynski, R.
        - Vienna, city of my dreams, Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 169/7)
        - [Wilderness road, orchestra] (Box 214)
      - Sinding, Christian
        - [Serenade, op. 56], Piano score and violin (2) parts (Box-folder 169/8)
        - [Suite, violin, orchestra, op. 10], Score (Box-folder 169/9)
        - [Suite, violin, orchestra, op. 10], Parts (Box-folder 169/10, Box-folder 170/1)
        - [Suite, violin, orchestra, op. 10; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 170/2)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 92], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 170/3)
      - Sinigaglia, Leone
        - [Étude de concert, string quartet, op. 5], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Étude de concert, string quartet, op. 5], Parts (Box-folder 170/4)
      - Sivori, Camillo
        - Eloge des larmes (melodie de Fr. Schubert), Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 170/5)
      - Slonimsky, Nicolas
        - Aromas de leyenda, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 170/6)
      - Smetana, Bedrich
        - [Aus der Heimat. no. 2], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 170/7)
        - Vlatava, Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Má vlast. Vlatava; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 170/8)
        - Prodaná nevesta, Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, E minor], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, E minor], Parts (Box-folder 170/9)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 15, G minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 170/10)
      - Smith, David Stanley
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 57, E-flat major], Score (Box-folder 171/1)
      - Smith, Frank M.
        - [Concertino in blue. Tempo di blues; arr.], Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 171/2)
      - Spalding, Albert
        - Alabama, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 171/3)
        - Berceuse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 171/4)
        - Etchings, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 171/5)
        - Wind in the pines, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 171/6)
      - Spohr, Louis
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 8, op. 47, A minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 171/7)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 8, op. 47, A minor], Miniature score (Box 214)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 8, op. 47, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 171/8, Box-folder 172/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 8, op. 47, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 172/2)